Friedman, Paul Collection of National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199 Miscellany 6062
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Paul Friedman Collection of National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199 Miscellany
1972-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Friedman, Paul
National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees (NUHHCE)
NUHHCE Local 1199
6062
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
Collection includes: organizing notebooks, organizing convention in 1973, desk calendars.
5791201
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 25, 2008
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Scope and Contents
Collection includes: organizing notebooks, organizing convention in 1973, desk calendars.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5854: Local 1199 Additional Records 5525: Local 1199 Additional Files 5680 OH: Local 1199 Oral History Project 6016: Local 1199 National Benefit and Pension Fund Records 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings
Health facilities -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State); National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199
5791201
- Correspondence, 1972-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Program., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Proposed Constitution., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Executive Director's Report., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Officers' Report., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Supplement to Officers' Report: Section I., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Supplement to Officers' Report: Section II., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Supplement to Officers' Report: Section III., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Supplement to Officers' Report: Section IV., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Supplement to Officers' Report: Section V., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Supplement to Officers' Report: Section VI., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NUHHCE Founding Convention-Memorabilia and Convention Tickets., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Benefits and Pension., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Staff Directories., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Clippings., 1972-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Leaflets, Flyers, Broadsides., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Subject File. (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Appointment Book., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Appointment Book., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Appointment Book., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Appointment Book., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Task Notes., 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Task Notes., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Task Notes., 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Task Notes., 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Task Notes., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Task Notes., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Task Notes., 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Task Notes., 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Task Notes. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Notes. (Box 1, Folder 31)